Guide to the Norman "Buddy" Baker Collection MSS.158
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Manuscript Scores by Buddy Baker
  - Christmas Album - Photocopies, Script, etc., 1974 Sep; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 8)
    annotated music breakdown and photocopy;typed script;photocopy "Being tight is not alright"; autograph black pencil 10 stave vocal leadsheets, yellow paper; autograph black pencil short scores with red,blue and green annotations, 12 stave yellow paper
    1-6, Finale
    Adair, Frances; Adair, Tom, 1913-1988; Walt Disney Productions
  - Crystal Caverns - Manuscripts, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 74)
    manuscript black pencil full score on 33 stave yellow paper with red and black annotations and whiteout corrections; music breakdown form
    SC#4-11A,13
    4fl,gr.fl,bassfl, 2clbasscl, 2bsn,6hn,3tpt,4tbn,tuba,tymp,cymb.,sn.dr.vibes,contrafl, piano,harp, strings
  - Daniel Boone - Escape to Paradise - Autographs, undated; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Sherman, Robert B. (Box 9)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch with red and green pencil annotations on white 12 stave paper; photocopies copyist piano conductor short scores interspersed with typed pages from script
    3051
    1B-XX
    Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; Walt Disney Productions; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-
  - Daniel Boone - Escape to Paradise - Photocopies (Box 9)
  - Daniel Boone - Wilderness Road - Autographs, 1960 June 6; 9 (Box 9)
    autograph black, blue, and red pencil 6 stave scores;photocopies copyist's piano conductor short scores, annotated in red
    3122
    1B-6D-V
    Walt Disney Productions; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; Victor, David
  - Daniel Boone - Wilderness Road - Photocopies (Box 9)
  - Deacon the High Noon Dog Cues 1A-4Bv,Q; Cues AC-6EV, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 75)
    autograph black pencil sketches on 12 yellow paper with red annotations; manuscript full score
    3679
    1A-6E(v)
  - Devil and Max Devlin - Cues 1-10 (Box 9)
  - Devil and Max Devlin - Notes, 1980 Nov 5, 11 (Box 9)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave yellow paper annotated in red and green ink;autograph spotting notes; anotated music breakdown sheets;other notes and correspondence
    0185
    1A-10E1
    Walt Disney Productions; Willis, Allee; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002
  - Devil and Max Devlin - Photocopies (Box 9)
  - Disney Billboards - Copies, Notes (Box 10)
  - Disney Billboards - Short scores, 1978 June Aug 7, 9, 11; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 10)
    autograph black pencil short score sketches on 12 stave yellow paper annotated in red pencil, and green, black and red ink; photocopies of copyist short scores; annotated music breakdown form, typed, annotated order of takes, orchestra call sheet, orchestra recording schedule, cutting record
    5904-354
    1-11
  - Disney on Parade - Autographs (Box 75)
  - Disney on Parade - Music breakdown sheets, 1 Aug, 10,13,14,17,18,20-21,25-26 Nov 1969 (Box 75)
    annotated forms, music breakdown,orchestra recording schedule; photocopy sketch score; photocopy piano conductor;autograph black pencil sketch on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; manuscript black pencil full score 33 stave on yellow paper with red annotations
    5969-042
    1A-3U,Dv-H
    2fl,ob,2cl,bsn, 3hn, 3tpt,3tbn,tuba,2perc,chorus,guitar,piano,harp, 4viol,8violas,4cello,3bass
    Cahn, Sammy; Walt Disney Productions; Washington, Ned, 1901-1976
  - Disney on Parade - Photocopies (Box 75)
  - Disney on Parade - Piano conductor - photocopies with annotations (Box 75)
  - Disneyland 10th Anniversary -Autograph - Cues 1B-1X, 2A-2K(v), undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 48)
    autograph 9 stave black pencil score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    3253
    1B-2Kv
  - Disneyland '61 - Autographs, 26-27 Ap 1961; 9 (Box 48)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations; typescript notes;photocopy piano conductor score
    3148;3314-609
    2A-3X
    Davies, Allen; Walt Disney Productions
  - Disneyland '61 - Piano conductor (Box 48)
  - Disneyland Showtime - Haunted Mansion, 1970 Feb 26; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 10)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red and green pencil and blue ink annotations; annotated order of takes
    3552
  - Disneyland the Park - Pecos Bill - Autographs, undated (Box 10)
    autograph black pencil four stave score sketch on 8 stave white paper annotated with red and blue pencil; photocopy copyist's piano conductor short scores
    5693
    1A - 3S
  - Disneyland the Park - Pecos Bill - photocopies, short scores (Box 10)
  - Disneyland Tokyo - Notes,scripts, etc., undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 11)
    typescript;photocopy full score
  - Disneyland Tokyo - Photocopies music, 1982 Aug 30; 7 (Box 11)
    photocopies full score and vocal lead sheets; autograph notes, photocopies script, music breakdown, frames per act
    Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; Walt Disney Productions; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Sherman, Robert B.
  - Disney's Wonderful World - Disney Billboards 79-80, 1979 Jun 16-20, Jul 10, 12 (Box 11)
    autograph Baker black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; Debney autogaph 6 stave score on 12 stave light yellow paper with red annotations; ms. Notes;annotated orchestra recording schedule;photocopy copyist's piano conductor short score
    5904-355
    OP C79,CX79,D,E79,EX79,EY79
    Walt Disney Productions; Klawitter, John
  - Donald and the Wheel - Autograph - Cues 1AA-2KK [1AA-2P], 12 May 1961; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 48)
    typescript;autograph sketch on white 12 stave paper with red annotations;autograph 9 stave score on yellow 18 stave paper with red annotations;photocopy composite sketch score; photocopy piano conductor
    2497
    1A-2P
  - Donald and the Wheel - Composite sketch (Box 48)
  - Donald and the Wheel - Piano conductor - photocopy with annotations (Box 48)
  - Donald in Mathmagicland - Autograph 6 Stave - short scores (Box 11)
  - Donald in Mathmagicland - Autograph Sketches, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 11)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red and green pencil annotations; autograph black pencil 6 stave short score on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; photocopies copyist short scores, Buddy's copy, Mixer's copy
    5755
    XX1-6,MT Pt.1-2,1A-3P
  - Donald in Mathmagicland - copies - mixer (Box 11)
  - Donald in Mathmagicland - copyist short scores - Buddy (Box 11)
  - Dream Called Magic, A, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 12)
    typed list of clicks per cue; annotated music breakdown form
    JH604035
  - Electric Co. - A Combo (Box 12)
  - Electric Co. - B Combo (Box 12)
  - Electric Co. - photocopy sketch (Box 12)
  - Electric Co. - Skytrap - Autographs, 1979 Mar 14-16; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 12)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on white 12 stave paper with red and blue magic marker annotations; photocopies short scores; photocopy order of takes
    3818 TV
    1-16
  - Elfego baca - Good and Bad, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    autograph black pencil 6 stave score on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green annotations
    5822
    1A-6xxx
  - Elfego Baca - Law and Order, Incorporated, 1958 Nov 6 (Box 13)
    photocopies copyists piano conductor shortscore with red pencil annotations
    5834
    1A-6B
    Walt Disney Productions; Dehr, Richard; Miller, Frank
  - Elfego Baca #6 - Griswold Murder, 1959 Jan 22; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    photocopy copyist piano conductor short score with red pencil annotations
    5845
    Leadin-1B-6B
  - Enchanted Snow Palace - Ballet #1-3, 1977 Aug 4; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    autograph black pencil 12 stave yellow paper, short score sketch with black ink annotations;photocopy copyist short score composite sketch
    J0787
  - Enchanted Snow Palace - Ballet #1-3 - photocopy (Box 13)
  - Energy Pavilion - Cues F1-F32.AA33 - photocopies (Box 77)
  - Energy Pavilion - Music Breakdown and misc., 25 Feb,25 Mar, 5 Apr 1982; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 76)
    typescript, annotated music breakdown, orchestra schedule; autograph black pencil 7 stave score on 14 stave yellow paper and 3 stave systems on 12 stave yellow paper with red and green annotations
    5910-023;5910-033;03-J-1707;03-J-1720; 03-1-5910-054
    1-18;1-21;1,3,4,5,CCS2,CCS8A-D,CCS10-11A,CCS13A-B,CCS15A-B,CCS16-17,SPINS;EPS1-14
  - Energy Pavilion - Piano conductor (Box 76)
  - Energy Pavilion - T.H. 1 & 2 - Autographs (Box 76)
  - Energy Pavilion - T.H. 1 & 2 - Piano conductor - annotated photocopy (Box 76)
  - Epcot French Pavilion - Photocopies with Annotated short scores (Box 77)
  - Epcot French Pavilion (England Session) Music Breakdown sheets 11, undated; 7 (Box 77)
    photocopy full scores; music breakdown sheets; photocopy piano conductor
    03-J-1717
    F2-F31
    Walt Disney Productions; Clements, Richard
  - Escapade in Florence - Autograph - Cues 1A-2B [2C-3G,4A-5C, 5D-6J], undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 49)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations; annotated photocopy piano conductor
    3170
    1A-6J
  - Escapade in Florence - Piano conductor - photocopy (Box 49)
  - Eternal Seas - Manuscript - full score (Box 77)
  - Eternal Seas - Piano conductor - photocopies with annotations, full score title music, 4 Jan 1982 (Box 77)
    photocopies short score and full score; manuscript black pencil full score with magic marker annotations
    5950.011
    1D,1X,M1,M8, 6,9-11,13
    Clements, Richard; Walt Disney Productions
  - Fantasy on Skis - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 50)
    Autograph black pencil 22stave score with red annotations; annotated copy piano conductor copyist's score; miscelleanous autograph scores
    3053
    1D,1G
  - Fantasy on Skis - Miscellaneous I & II (Box 50)
  - Fantasy on Skis - Piano conductor (Box 50)
  - Feather Farm - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 50)
    black pencil 12 stave sketch on white paper with red pencil annotations; pencil lead sheet with red annotations on yellow 10 stave paper; pencil score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    1A-D,2A-F;3A-F
  - Fire on Kelly mountain - Autograph, 1973 Aug 13-17; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave yellow paper with red pencil and red magic marker annotations; annotated break down sheet, orchestra schedule
    3678
  - Fire on Kelly mountain - Breakdown (Box 13)
  - First Fifty Years - U.S.C. - Autographs, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 77)
    autograph black pencil 12 stave short score annotated in red; autograph black pencil full score on 33 stave yellow paper; photocopy short score
    Melodrama;Professors;Bernie;All Hail #4;Alma Mater #2
    2fl,ob,Eng.hn,2cl,2bsn,4hn,2tpt,3tbn,2perc,piano,harp,strings
    Schaefer, Will; Walt Disney Productions
  - Flo Daniels 204 shorts - copies, 1976 Oct 19; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    photocopies of cues from other pictures as well as two pages lead sheets
    BJ-123
  - Footloose Goose - Autograph (Box 13)
  - Footloose Goose - TV Breakdown, 1974 Oct 9-10; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 13)
    autograph black pencil on 12 stave yellow paper with red, green and blue annotations; photocopy typed list of order of takes, annotated music break down list
    3709
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Boy's Republic -Autograph (Box 14)
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Boy's Republic -Autograph (Box 14)
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Glassblower - Autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; photocopy full score
    8232-005
    A,1-9B
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Glassblower - Photocopies (Box 14)
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Little Circus - 8232-003 - Autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; photocopies full score
    8232-003
    A,1-19
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Little Circus - 8232-003 - Photocopies (Box 14)
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Miscellaneous, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil sketches on 10, 12 and 14 stave white and yellow paper
    11, Unnumbered
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Venice -8232-004 -autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red and blue annotations;photocopies full score
    8232-004
    A,1-12B
  - Foreign Correspondent - Italy - Venice -8232-004 -photocopies (Box 14)
  - Foreign Correspondent - Japan (copies) 8224-001 - 8224-005, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    photocopy copyist piano conductor short score
    8224-001 - 8224-005
    1A-1H
  - Foreign Correspondent - Rome 8232-002, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil short score sketches on 12 stave white paper with red pencil annotations
    8232-002
    1-12B
  - Foreign Correspondent -Italy - Autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 11 (Box 14)
    autograph black pencil short score sketch on 12 stave white paper with red pencil annotations
    8232-001
    A-B,4, 11
  - Fourth Anniversary Show - piano conductor - photocopy, undated; 5 (Box 15)
    photocopy copyist's piano conductor short score
    1A-6F3
  - Fox and Hound - Cues 1E,1D, 2A, 2F, 5B, 95 - short scores (Box 78)
  - Fox and Hound - "Baby Fox" - Cue 1D - Orchestral parts - photocopy (Box 80)
  - Fox and Hound - "Leaves fall" - Orchestral parts - photocopy (Box 80)
  - Fox and Hound - Arrangement A - Conductor folder, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 83)
    photocopies copyist parts and score
    0136
    1B,1D,2A,2F,5B,5G,7F
    picc,3fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,2bsn,4hn,,3tpt,4tbn,,glock,4perc,harmonica,guitar,celeste,harp,organ or synth,strings (0,0,0,4,4)
  - Fox and Hound - Arrangement A - Orchestral Parts (Box 82)
  - Fox and Hound - Arrangement B - Orchestral Parts (Box 83)
  - Fox and Hound - Band Version - Cues 1B,1C,1D,2A,2F,5B,5G,7F, 9E Manuscript full scores, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 81)
    black pencil full 33 stave score for band annotated in red and green and blue magic marker
    1B,1C,1D,2A,2F,5B, 5G,7F,9E
  - Fox and Hound - Ces 5B,5G, 7F, 9E -orchestral scores - annotated photocopy and autograph (Box 79)
  - Fox and Hound - Cue 1B/1C - [Forest/ Wilderness] Orchestral Parts - Manuscript and photocopies, 1980,1981; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 80)
    black pencil orchestral parts and photocopies
    1B,1C,1D, 9E
    picc,3fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,2bsn,4hn,,3tpt,4tbn,,glock,4perc,harmonica,guitar,celeste,harp,organ or synth,strings (0,0,0,4,4),fenderbass
  - Fox and Hound - Cue 9E - Orchestral parts (Box 80)
  - Fox and Hound - Cue 9E - piano conductor with annotation and photocopy full score - 2, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 79)
    black pencil 33 stave full score with red and green annotations; photocopies scores and parts
    1B,2A,5B,5G,7F,9E, F9-F31
    3fl,2ob,Enghn,2cl,basscl, 2bsn,5hn,flugelhorn,4tpt,4tbn,tuba,vibraphone,glock,perc,harmonica,guitar,celeste,harp,organ or synth,strings (6,6,6,4,2),fenderbass
  - Fox and Hound - Cues 1A-11E - Autograph short scores (Box 78)
  - Fox and Hound - Cues 1B, 2A - orchestral scores - annotated photocopy and autograph (Box 79)
  - Fox and Hound - Cues F9-F31 Photocopy full score (Box 79)
  - Fox and Hound - Forest ballet - Photocopy of autograph short score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 84)
    photocopies of orchestral parts
    1B,1C,1D,2A,2F,5B,5G,9E
    picc,3fl,2ob,2cl,basscl,2bsn,4hn,,3tpt,4tbn,,glock,4perc,harmonica,guitar,celeste,harp,organorsynth,strings (6,6,4,4,2),electric bass
  - Fox and Hound - Music breakdown, order of takes, recording schedule, typescript Harmony, 24 Jul 1980, 1-3 Ap 1981; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 78)
    annotated music breakdown, order of takes,recording schedule, typescript Harmony; photocopy copyist piano conductor
    1A-11E
    3fl,ob,3cl,bsn,5hn,flugelhorn,4tpt,4tbn,tuba,glock,perc,harmonica,guitar,celeste,harp,organorsynth,strings (6,6,6,4,2),fenderbass
  - Fox and Hound - Photocopy of copyist's orchestral parts (Box 84)
  - Fox and Hound - Piano conductor with some annotation (Box 78)
  - Fox and Hound - Repeat cues - photocopies - full scores (Box 81)
  - Fox that never left home - Autographs -Cues 1A-3D1, 1978 June 20-21; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 15)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with blue,red and green annotations; annotated music breakdown form; typed orchestra schedule; typed order of takes;photocopy reduced autograph short score
    3823
    1A-6C1
  - Gnome-mobile - Music Breakdown, etc., 1967 Feb 13-15; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 7 (Box 16)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red pencil annotations; annotated music break down form; notes; typed orchestra schedule;photocopy piano conductor short score
    2193
    1A-10KV
  - Gnome-mobile - Temp - Cues - Autographs 1A-10VV (Box 16)
  - Gnome-mobile - Temp - Cues - Photocopies 1A-10VV (Box 16)
  - Golden Horseshoe - Autograph, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 1 (Box 51)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    3182
    2C-6G
  - Great bear sled dog race - Autographs, 1977 Jun 14--15; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 16)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave yellow paper with blue, green and red annotations; annotated music breakdown form; typed order of takes
    3798
    1A-5E
  - Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow - "Buddy Baker's Copy" - Annotated full score (Box 52)
  - Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow - "Innoventions" - Misc. (Box 52)
  - Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow - Autographs - Home, Transportation, Info, Entertainment, Sports, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 52)
    autograph black pencil sketchscore on 12 stave yellow paper with blue and red annotations; autograph 9 stave score on 18 stave white paper with blue and red annotations;typescript; 3 in floppy computer disc; printed music;autograph revised sketches on 12 stave white and yellow paper;photocopies full score
    81-036-10-50
    1A, 1-5
  - Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow - Cue 1A - Autograph (Box 52)
  - Great Big Beautiful Tomorrow - Cue 1A - Photocopies Full Score (Box 52)
  - Great Mouse Detective, The - Shooting script, autograph cue sheets, 1986 Feb 18; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 17)
    autograph click track notes, cue sheet; photocopy shooting script; correspondence
  - Guns in the Heather - Autographs - Cues 1A-9D2 [1A-17H(2)], 1968 Nov; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 17)
    autograph black pencil short score on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; annotated order of takes form
    3525
    1A(L)-17H(L)
  - Holiday in Samoa, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 17)
    photocopy piano conductor copyist short score
    8225; 8247-001-0014
    A1-5E
  - Holiday Time at Disneyland, undated (Box 17)
    autograph black pencil vocal short scores on 12 stave white paper with red annotations; photocopy copyist piano conductor short score
    3185
    1A(v)-6Kv2
  - Hot lead and cold feet - Autographs - Cues 1A-10G (Box 18)
  - Hot lead and cold feet - Music breakdown sheets, etc., 1978 Ap 3-13; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 8 (Box 18)
    autograph black pencil short scoreon 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; annotated music breakdown, order of takes, orchestra schedule, memo;annotated photocopy copyist piano conductor short score
    0160
    1A-10G
  - Hot lead and cold feet - Photocopies with Annotations - Cues 1A-10G (Box 18)
  - Hunting Instinct, The - Autograph full score, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 2 (Box 53)
    annotated music breakdown;autograph black pencil 9 stave score on yellow 18 stave paper with red annotations;annotated photocopy piano conductor
    3099
    1A-7C
  - Hunting Instinct, The - Piano conductor with annotations (Box 53)
  - Impressions of France - Annotated piano conductor (Box 54)
  - Impressions of France - Autograph sketches -Session II, 7 Dec 1981; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 7 (Box 54)
    autograph black pencil sketch on 12 stave yellow paper with red annotations; printed full scores with annotations;photocopy piano conductor; printed French scores;music breakdown
    F1,F9-13,F14-16A,F19-F28,F30-32
  - Impressions of France - Medley for Band (Box 55)
  - Impressions of France - Medley for Band - Full set of parts (Box 55)
  - Impressions of France - Medley for Orchestra (Box 55)
  - Impressions of France - Photocopied score and orchestral parts, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 56)
    orchestral parts
  - Impressions of France - Piano conductor and photocopy sketches - Cues F1-F33v(1), undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 55)
    photocopy piano conductor short score; photocopy autograph sketches;photocopy full score; autograph black pencil sketches;photocopy orchestral parts
    F1-F33v(1)
  - Impressions of France - Scores I-III (Box 54)
  - Impressions of France - Sketches, photos, negatives - Piano conductor and full orchestral scores - Session I (Box 54)
  - Impressions of France - Suites 1-6 Orchestral parts for Woodwinds, Brass, Percussion, Strings (Box 56)
  - Inside Donald Duck - Autograph TV527, 19Sep 1961; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 5 (Box 57)
    autograph 9 stave black pencil score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations;annotated piano conductor score
    3101
    1A-7J(1)
  - Inside Donald Duck - Piano conductor (Box 57)
  - It's a small world - full score - highlighted photocopy (Box 19)
  - It's a small world - manuscript (1 p. autograph), 1971 Aug 12, 20; Sherman, Robert B.; 6 (Box 19)
    manuscript pencil score, arr. Marks; annotated music breakdown, order of takes, memo, notes and orchestra schedule;highlighted photocopy full score;photocopy piano conductor cue 5, 7, 7A, 11,12
    0F07-002
    Walt Disney Productions; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Hammack, Bobby; Hammack, Bobby
  - It's a small world - Piano conductor - Photocopies (Box 19)
  - Johnny Shiloh - Photocopies - piano conductor (Box 57)
  - Johnny Shiloh Part I - Autograph - Cues 1A-6E, 23 May 1962 (Box 57)
    autograph black pencil 9 stave score on 18 stave yellow paper with red annotations; typescript lyrics; leadsheet; autograph sketches on 12 stave yellow paper; photocopy piano conductor
    3126
    1A-6E;7A-12F
    Walt Disney Productions; Sherman, Richard M., 1928-; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; Sherman, Robert B.
  - Johnny Shiloh Part II - Autographs - Cues 7A-12F (Box 57)
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - "Crystal Caverns" - sketches - copy (Box 86)
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - "Unload exit" - Autograph sketches and breakdown (Box 86)
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - Bound Full Score - reduced photocopy (Box 85)
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - Full annotated sketches - photocopy (Box 85)
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - Main theme and Variations Prod. # SC.1, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 6 (Box 86)
    photocopies
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - Manuscript full score I & II, undated; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 85)
    photocopy full score and sketches; manuscript black pencil full score on 33 stave yellow paper with red annotations
    SC. 4-14
  - Journey to the Center of the Earth - Scores recorded in London - photocopy (Box 86)
  - Jungle book, 25 May 1970; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002; 4 (Box 58)
    autograph black pencil on 12 stave white paper;annotated piano conductor;lead sheet and misc. material
    5930-200
  - Kids is Kids - Autographs 531-TV, 17 Oct 1961; Baker, Buddy, 1918-2002 (Box 58)